(Penny:)I know.
(Todd:)I've always wanted one.
(door slams)
(Sheldon:)Well, he's even more cunning
than we thought.
(Sheldon:)You know, the joke's on him.
(Sheldon:)Without the certificate of
authenticity,
(Sheldon:)that bat'leth is worthless.
(Howard:)Yeah, he walked
right into our trap.
(Raj:)Legoland seems like
a hollow dream now.
(Leonard(phone rings):)Uh-oh.
(Raj:)What's the matter?
Something's wrong.
(Leonard:)I'm not getting any gas.
(rattling)
(Leonard:)Anybody know anything about
internal combustion engines?
(Sheldon:)Of course.
(Howard:)19th-century technology.
Very basic.
(Leonard:)Does anybody know how to fix
an internal combustion engine?
(Leonard:)No. No.
Not a clue.
(Leonard:)Well, we'd better call somebody
to come pick us up.